Boss.
[Eclipse in the Lost City]
[Episode 17]
Lu Ye.
You really are something
You can even survive this.
Chief Xu, you flatter me.
I haven't killed you yet.
How could I die?
You are still too young.
If you kill me,
you will never know how your father died.
It doesn't matter.
After fighting for so long,
I'm already tired.
Save your words for the road
to the underworld.
Farewell.
Tianbai.
Tianbai!
Hurry!
Get him to emergency, quick!
Lu Ye.
You can't escape.
Is that so?
It seems Chief Xu is determined
to kill me today.
That's right.
Then I have no choice anymore.
I can only let your daughter, Miss Xu Yin,
die with me.
What...
What did you do?
Nothing much.
Chief Xu has been so hospitable.
I naturally have to return the favor.
It's just some hospitality.
[Xu Qingdao's daughter, Xu Yin]
Miss Xu Yin.
The Chief specially sent us to
pick you up.
Please.
Let me go.
I remember Miss Xu's train arrives
at nine.
If I'm not back at the Qingtian Gang
by ten,
I'm afraid you'll only see her corpse.
Let me see how many minutes are left.
Chief Xu,
do you want to bet
if I'm telling the truth?
Take him back to the Qingtian Gang
to exchange for my daughter.
Chief...
Do I need to repeat myself?
Listen up, everyone.
Send him back unharmed
and bring the Miss Xu back safely.
Yes.
Such a deep father-daughter bond.
Young Master.
Uncle Zhong.
Be careful.
Don't hurt Miss Xu.
You.
Don't move.
Listen up, you over there.
I'll count to three,
and we let go at the same time.
Three.
Two.
One.
Miss Xu.
You had such a big scare
right after returning to the country.
I'm really sorry
This will hurt a little.
All done.
Young Master.
How many times have I told you
to take care of yourself?
Take care of yourself.
Look.
How did you end up like this again?
And Shen Tianbai, too.
Wasn't it supposed to be just an act?
Why did he hit so hard?
This kid...
Uncle Zhong.
Don't worry.
He's hurt worse than I am.
I shot him.
But taking this bullet was worth it.
Although there was a slight hiccup,
it's still within the plan.
He took a fatal shot for Xu Qingdao.
Now he is Xu Qingdao's
most trusted subordinate.
Do you remember?
We used to fight in school.
We are friends.
Chief.
Tianbai.
I owe you this time.
You saved my life.
Chief,
it's my duty.
As long as you're fine.
Good.
I knew I was right about you.
Things in Ningcheng
are about to change.
But you and I are in the same boat
after all.
Yes.
Get some rest first.
As for the rest,
once you recover,
we'll discuss it further.
Yes, Chief.
Yin.
Father!
Are you okay?
Let me see.
Father.
I thought I would never see you again.
Glad you're safe.
Did the Qingtian Gang do anything to you?
No.
With you here, they wouldn't dare.
Yes.
Father, I'm so glad you came to save me.
Silly girl.
You are my only daughter.
Your life is more important than anything.
Come.
Sit down.
Yin.
You've been studying abroad
all these years.
I've always been worried about you.
I'm getting old now.
I just hope you can stay in Ningcheng
and stay by my side.
Okay?
Okay.
I'll stay by your side
and won't go anywhere.
Silly girl.
How can you stay by my side forever?
When you reach the right age,
you'll have to get married.
Father.
I've already found the best candidate
for you.
His name is Shen Tianbai.
He just saved my life.
He has a bright future.
You'll definitely like him.
Okay.
I'll listen to you.
Go and bring him some medicine.
You really are my good daughter.
I'll go then.
Since you're awake,
stop pretending to be asleep.
Hello, Xu Yin.
Miss Xu.
You're so formal.
Do you know why my father called me here?
You saved his life.
Now you are his most trusted confidant.
He wants me to marry you
to tie you firmly to the Shisha Gang.
You must be joking, Miss Xu.
To him,
I am just an object.
Who to give me to, when to give me,
and what benefits it can bring
are all calculated clearly.
But rather than being someone's wife,
I'd rather be the chief of Shisha Gang.
Miss Xu.
What does this mean?
Time is tight,
so I'll get straight to the point.
I'm here to deliver a letter for Lu Ye.
Young Master,
although Miss Xu Yin
is your college classmate,
she is Xu Qingdao's daughter after all.
What if...
Don't worry.
She hates Xu Qingdao just as much as I do.
Do you remember
how Xu Qingdao became the leader
of the Shisha Gang?
I remember the former leader
didn't favor him,
but his sworn brother.
Later, that man died in an accident,
and Xu Qingdao naturally took over.
Was it not an accident?
His sworn brother was Xu Yin's uncle.
After Xu Yin's mother found out about it,
she wanted to make the truth public,
but he silenced her.
He not only killed them,
but also took their property.
He used that money to secure his position.
Xu Yin was still young back then.
He probably thought a child
wouldn't remember anything.
In fact, she hasn't forgotten
for a single day.
I see.
In that case,
Miss Xu Yin going abroad to lay low
was indeed a wise move.
Xu Qingdao asked Xu Yin to come back
this time
for another reason.
[Medical Report, Xu Qingdao]
Xu Qingdao is sick.
No,
he...
he wants his daughter to give him
a kidney?
Even a cornered rabbit will bite,
not to mention she's no pushover.